《闪电侠》前情回顾
Previously on "The Flash"...
威尔斯委员会
Council of Wells.
多元宇宙中最聪明的头脑
Some of the brightest minds in all the multiverse.
这里显示还有另外一股低温异常
There's still another cryogenic anomaly
存在于我的DNA中
in my DNA.
冰霜杀手还在你体内
Killer Frost is still a part of you.
我越多的想要使用我的大脑
The more I try to use my brain,
我就会越快失去它
the sooner I'm going to lose it.
他们知道迪沃想做什么了
They know what DeVoe's doing.
分散的卫星为了一个目的同时运行
Separate satellites working together for a single purpose?
迪沃想要移除地球上所有人的智慧
DeVoe wants to remove the intelligence of everyone on Earth?
就像我这样
Just like mine.
爱瑞丝
Iris?
抱歉  宝贝  接着睡吧
Sorry, babe! Go back to sleep.
爱瑞丝
Iris--
就等一下  让我
Just one second. Let me just--
让我写完最后一句
let me just get this last sentence down, okay?
你为什么还没睡  这些是什么
Why--why are you still awake? What is all this?
这是
This is...
我能找到的和迪沃有关的所有
every file, every report, every footnote
文件  报告和脚注
that I could find on DeVoe.
我半夜醒了以后就把它们翻出来了
I dug it all up when I woke up in the middle of the night.
我就是没法停止思考迪沃和他的机器的事情
I just--I couldn't stop thinking about DeVoe and his machine.
现在他还有了所有的卫星
And now that he has all of the satellites,
水星实验室劫案
三台量子计算机失窃
他随时有可能启动那台机器
I mean, he could turn on the machine at any point.
不知道具体时间简直令人发疯
And not knowing is maddening,
但起码我知道他计划做什么
but at least I know what he's planned, right?
但城里的其他人都不知道
But everyone else in the city, they are oblivious.
这就是我决定为此写篇文章的原因
Which is why I decided that I need to write a piece about it.
-文章  -曝光他那个疯狂计划的每个细节
- An article? - Exposing every single detail of his maniacal plan.
假如中城的人知道他要干什么
I think that if people in this city knew what he was up to,
那么也许他们可以自卫
then maybe they could protect themselves.
巴里  我认为这就是我们要逆转对迪沃的
Barry, I really think this is exactly what we need
局势所需要的
to change the tide against DeVoe.
我要上楼
So I'm gonna go upstairs,
洗个澡  等我回来时
I'm gonna take a shower, and when I come back,
你得告诉我你对迪沃那张会飞的椅子
I need you to tell me everything you know about
以及他怎么用它跳跃空间所知道的一切
that flying chair and how he uses it to body hop and...
闪 电 侠
第四季
第二十一集
昨晚哈里  西斯科和我
So last night, Harry, Cisco, and I
熬了一整夜编写各种我们能想到的
were up all night writing all the different algorithms
和迪沃偷窃的卫星
we could think of involving
结果:五单位
有关的算法
the satellite tech that DeVoe stole.
我们认为迪沃计划把他的五颗卫星
We think DeVoe plans to position each
分别发射到绕地球轨道的
of his five satellites at specifically calculated
特定位置
points around the globe.
等每个卫星上的量子计算机串联时
And when the quantum computers in each satellite link up--
他就会用这种连接发射
He'll use that network to basically emit
一系列大量暗物质
a series of dark matter bursts.
那就会重启地球上每个
That will reboot the pre-frontal cortex
男女老幼的前额皮质
of every man, woman, and child on this Earth.
我们得把它掐死在萌芽中
Well, we need to nip this in the bud.
我们不能让他发射这些卫星
We can't let him launch those satellites.
但我们要怎么找到他
Yeah, but I mean, how are we supposed to find him?
我们都好几天没能
I mean, we haven't been able to register
探测到迪沃的口袋维度能量了
DeVoe's pocket dimension energy for days.
并且有了纳尔操纵重力的能力
And with Null's gravitational powers,
他随时随地都可以发射这些卫星
he can launch these satellites from any place at any time.
对  他可以
Yeah, he can.
你想什么呢  巴仔
What are you thinking, Bar?
我们要把他们打下来
I think we shoot 'em down.
有个小问题
There is one small problem.
迪沃有基尔戈的超能力
DeVoe has Kilgore's powers.
对  他可以控制我们用来向他们开火的
Yeah, he can manipulate any tech-based weapon
所有科技武器
we fire at him.
所以我们不用科技
So we don't use tech.
我们用某种有机武器
We use some kind of organic matter weapon.
对  比如
Right, like a...
比如
like a...
我们分头行动吧
You know what? Let's split up,
看看能发现什么
see what we can find.
拉蒙
Ramon.
迪沃没有行动  他为什么没有行动
DeVoe's not acting. Why is he not acting?
我不知道  但这不重要
I don't know, but it doesn't matter.
但这很重要  要是我还有我的智力
But it does matter, though. And if I had my intelligence,
我能找出原因  但我没有
I could figure that out. But I don't.
-我得恢复智力  -不
- I got to get it back. - No, no, no.
你要做的就是耐心
What you need to do is be patient.
我们会咨询
We're consulting with, like,
我们认识的每一个科学家
literally every scientist we know.
你为什么不咨询我
Why don't you consult with me?
不  哈里
No. Harry...
不  不是这个傻瓜的我  是另外的我
No, not dumb me, the other mes.
威尔斯委员会
The council.
我必须承认你的传送装置
So I must admit, found your transmission
特别有意思
intriguing, to say the least.
但首先
But first...
我有个问题要问你  哈里·威尔斯
I have a question for you, Harry Wells.
告诉我  哈里  你设计的
Tell me, Harry, how does your "Hypothetica""
思考帽是怎么进行
thinking cap account for
暗物质的磁耦合谐振运输的
the resonant inductive coupling of the dark matter transfer?
-磁  -我跟你说话了吗
- Well, the--the inductive-- - Am I speaking to you?
我想不起来了  等等  我没跟你说话
I cannot remember. Oh, wait. I'm not.
这个小家伙肯定是西斯科  把你装进盒子
The little guy that must be Cisco, put you in the box.
把盒子装进口袋
Put the box in the pocket.
问哈里一个简单问题
Talking to Harry, a simple question.
它怎么进行磁耦合谐振的
How does it account for the resonant coupling?
它
It, uh...
我知道了  他不知道
I knew it! He doesn't know!
他不知道
He doesn't know!
单纯的哈里现在是头脑简单的哈里了
Simple Harry is truly Simple Harry now.
-不  这不是  -记住
- No. That's not what's hap-- - Ja, remember,
我把你放盒子里  把盒子放口袋里
I put you in the box. Put the box in the pocket.
在口袋里碾碎盒子
Crush the box! In the pocket.
是这么回事啊
This is very simple what has happened.
你设计的思考帽故障了
Your "Hypothetical" Thinking cap has malfunctioned, hmm,
并且把世上曾经的一个天才
and left the world's once formidable intellect
变成了傻瓜
a dum-dum!
-不是这样的  -就是这样的
- That's not what happened. - Yeah, that's what happened.
就是这样的
That's what happened.
可怜的哈里
Poor Harry.
-威尔斯先生  -是的
- Herr Wells... - Ja.
你到底帮不帮我们
Are you gonna help us or not?
-不帮  -为什么
- Not. - Why not?
威尔斯委员会集合了智慧超群之人
The Council of Wells is a council of superior intellects
接受其他智慧超群之人的挑战
there to accept the challenge of others with superior intellects.
它叫做威尔斯委员会
It's called the Council of Wells
而不是蠢才委员会
and not the Council of Dum-Dums!
-看看他  -在看
- Loot at this man. - I see him.
他不是你们的一员吗
Is he not one of your own?
你是在告诉我你要背叛你们其中的一员
Are you telling me you're gonna betray one of your own
就因为他不符合这些随心所欲的智慧标准吗
because he doesn't meet some arbitrary intellectual standard?
所以你是明白的
Ah! So you do understand.
没错  和你这位头脑简单的朋友不同
Ja, unlike your simple friend,
这就是你现在必须考虑的事
here's what you now must consider.
再见
Auf Wiedersehen!
不  他说得对  我的确是个蠢材
No, he's right. I am a dum-dum.
你不是蠢材
Hey, you are not a dum-dum.
拉蒙  拜托  面对现实吧
Ramon, come on. Let's face facts.
我失去了大部分的科学和数学知识
I've lost most of my science, lost most of my math.
接下来轮到语言  而我们却束手无策
Language will be next, and there's nothing we can do about it.
正好相反  我的朋友
On the contrary, "Mon frery"
最初是我们设立了蠢蛋委员会
we're the ones who created that council of ding-dongs
所以如果他们不帮我们
in the first place, so if they're not gonna help us,
那我们只剩下另一个选择
that leaves us with one other option.
设立一个全新且更聪明的委员会
A new council, a smarter council.
一个更好的委员会
A better council.
凯特琳
Hey, Caitlin.
你有止痛药吗
Do you have any ibuprofen?
看着这些有机物质
Reading up on all this organic matter
让我患上了有机偏头痛
has given me an organic migraine.
谢了
Oh, thanks.
你脑门上有一根...
You have a little...
是针灸
Oh! Acupuncture.
自从我发现
Ever since I found out
我的DNA里还存在低温异常现象时
I still have a cryogenic anomaly in my DNA,
我一直在用我所能想到的每一个医疗方法
I've been doing every medical avenue I can think of
不让冰霜杀手冒出苗头
to get Killer Frost to emerge.
你真的很想她吧
Mm. You really do miss her, don't you?
是的  冰霜杀手曾经是我的一部分
Yeah. Killer Frost was a part of me,
在我开始接受她的时候
and just as I was starting to accept her,
她就被夺走了
she was taken away.
我已经没有办法了
I'm running out of ideas.
我知道这不完全一样
Well, I know it's not exactly the same,
但我也碰到过失踪人口的案子
but I've had my fair share of missing persons cases.
那碰壁的时候你怎么做
And what do you do when you've hit a wall?
我会试着从一个不同的方向去出击
I try to attack it from a different direction.
如果这样能帮到你的话  总之谢谢你
If that helps. Anyway, thanks.
我们一直从错误的方向出击
We've been attacking this from the wrong direction.
我们需要零科技装置
We know we need a tech-free projectile
来阻止迪沃的卫星
to stop DeVoe's satellites,
所以我们一直在找物体
so we've been looking for an object
其实我们真正需要的是人
when what we really need is a person.
阿姆内特
Amunet.
阿姆内特·布莱克
Amunet Black?
我知道她不是理想的选择
I know she's not the ideal choice,
但是阿姆内特的通灵亚力可碎片
but Amunet's psychic-powered alnico shards
不仅有致命的力量
are not only deadly powerful.
而且对迪沃的基尔戈超能力完全免疫
They're completely immune to DeVoe's Kilgore powers.
不理想  她可是绑架过你呢
Not ideal? I mean, she kidnapped you.
她想把我当超能力者奴隶给卖掉
She tried to sell me into meta slavery.
她还毁了我的单身派对
And she ruined my bachelorette party, I mean...
-那不是...  -你说得对
- That's not... - I mean, you're right.
当然这并不是什么大事
It's-- it's admittedly not as big of a deal,
但是你明白我的意思
but you know what I'm saying.
我们不能和阿姆内特联手  她是罪犯
Yeah, we can't partner up with Amunet. She's a criminal.
史纳特和冰霜杀手也是罪犯
Snart's a criminal. So's Killer Frost.
我们都与他们联手过
We worked with them.
即使我们原谅阿姆内特所做的一切
Look, even if we forgave Amunet for everything she's done...
要原谅的可多了
Which is a lot.
你为什么觉得她会愿意帮我们
What makes you say she'd be willing to help us?
我见过她的另一面
I've seen a different side of her.
她之前帮过我
She's helped me before,
我相信她会再帮忙的
and I believe she'll do it again.
阿姆内特的藏身之所和我想的不太一样啊
This isn't what I expected Amunet's hideout to look like.
我也许做了一点改变
I might have made a few changes.
不是吧
Really, boys?
你想害死我们吗  他可是闪电侠啊  笨蛋
You trying to get us killed? That's The Flash, you morons.
凯特琳也许看着像图书管理员
And Caitlin may look like a librarian,
但她可是冷酷无情的野兽
but she's a coldhearted beast.
阿姆内特在哪
Where's Amunet?
不是吧  不先说一句你好吗  诺瓦克
Really? No, "Hello, Norvock. How you been?"
甚至都不给我介绍一下你的新老大吗
You're not even gonna introduce me to your new boss?
我不是她的老大  我只是她的朋友
Oh, I'm not her boss. I'm just a friend.
这话说得真好听
Well, isn't that sweet?
诺瓦克  阿姆内特在哪
Norvock, where's Amunet?
几个月都没人见过她
No one's heard a peep from her in months.
据我所知  那女巫死了
For all I know, the witch is dead.
阿姆内特不见了吗
So Amunet's gone?
显然在她和沃夫监狱长的交易
Well, apparently after her deal
谈崩了之后
with Warden Wolfe took a nosedive,
她已经不再贩卖超能力者了
she's been out of the meta trafficking business.
凯特琳  你有没有任何
Caitlin, do you know any personal details
能帮我们查到她下落的个人资料吗
that can help us track her down?
我不知道
Oh, I don't know.
阿姆内特一直都是一个不喜欢谈私事的人
Amunet's always been a private person,
有些难以捉摸  不顾后果
sort of unpredictable and rash,
凭感觉行事
kind of fly by the seat of your pants.
她圣诞节绑架我的时候
You know, when she kidnapped me at Christmas,
她说她以前做过空中乘务员
she said she used to be a flight attendant.
粒子加速器爆炸的那晚
I think she was on an airplane the night
她好像正在搭乘飞机
the particle accelerator exploded.
这我们可以查一查  我看看
Okay, that we can work with. Let's see.
粒子加速器爆炸的那晚
Yeah, it looks like there were 35 flights in the air
中城好像有35个航班在飞行
in Central City the night of the particle accelerator explosion.
西斯科  你能拿到航班清单吗
Cisco, can you access the flight manifests?
能  而且我可以把航速证明...
Yes, I can, and I can take the cruise credentials--
放在面部识别软件上做交叉对比吗
Cross-reference them in the facial recognition?
你能别读心吗
Can you not read my mind?
她的正名叫莱斯莉·乔科伊吗
Her real name is Leslie Jocoy?
也许她在航班上用的是真名  不是假名
Maybe she's operating under her real name, not her pseudonym.
在粒子加速器爆炸之后
Well, she didn't have a criminal record
她才有了犯罪记录
until the particle accelerator,
-所以  不是个太差的计划  -对
- so...it's not a bad plan. - Right.
中城警局的数据库里有着
CCPD's database has several
好几个莱斯莉·乔科伊之前的工作地址
prior work addresses for Leslie Jocoy.
好吧  咱们去一一查看下吧
All right, let's pay 'em all a visit.
好吧  爸爸你和凯瑟琳去查看下
Okay. Dad why don't you and Caitlin go check out
-最近期的地址  -我去查剩下的
- the most recent address? - I'll check out the rest.
听起来可以
Sounds like a plan.
我应该回阁楼去了
And I should get back to the loft.
我需要拿个迪沃的资料来写文章
I need to pick up a DeVoe file for my article-
对了  我能和你简单说两句吗
Hey, actually, can I just talk to you really quick?
行啊  好
Um, yeah. Okay.
就是关于你文章的  我觉得也许
Just about your article. I just think maybe
告诉所有人一个超级天才超能力者
telling everybody about a meta-human uber-genius
计划要重启人们的大脑...
who plans on rebooting people's brains--
是  但如果我不告诉他们
Yeah, but if we don't tell them,
他们发现时就可能太晚了
they might find out when it's too late.
是  但我不  我是说小队总是喜欢
Sure, but I don't- I mean, the team's always liked
低调的做事
to keep what we're working on low-key.
好吧  我就按照他们的想法来
Okay, well, I'll run the idea by them.
不  我不是说别写  我就是说
No. I-I don't mean no. I just mean...
也许可以等着写完再说
maybe hold off until you finish writing it.
好吧  我先等等
Okay. Yeah, I'll hold off.
-真的吗  -是的
- You will? - Yeah.
我懂的  我们从来没有和
No, I mean, I get it. We've never openly shared
这座城公开分享过这一类的信息
this kind of information with the city before,
而且小队在看过我写完的文章后
and the team will be more likely to agree with me
很可能会更同意我的想法
if I have a full article ready for them to read.
所以我准备抓紧完成
So I am gonna hurry up and finish it.
-好的  -谢谢
- Okay. - Thanks.
哈里  来见一见
Harry, I give to you...
精通情感的"哈里森委员会"
the emotionally astute Council of Harrisons.
你来了呀
Hey. There ya are.
H威尔斯  你在这里做什么
H. Wells, what--what are you doing here?
那些老古董  他们厌倦了我的
Those other stiffs, well, they got tired
联系
of my connections
让我对他们的派对感到厌倦  所以...
making me tardy to their party, so...
他们就踢了我
They gave me the boot.
把你给  等下  所以我不是唯一一个
Gave you the--wait, so I'm not the only one?
我们都被踢出队伍了
Nuh-uh, all of us been kicked out.
你们都被踢...
All of you have been kick--
你给我找了一群弃儿委员会啊
you got me a council of rejects.
他们都是聪明的弃儿
Well, they're brilliant rejects.
你叫谁弃儿呢  看看这家伙
Who you calling rejects? 'Ey, look at this guy.
你以为你是谁
What are you, sta-nuts?
容许我介绍下自己
Allow myself to introduce myself.
索尼·威尔斯  地球二十四
Sonny Wells. Earth-24.
为您效劳  他们叫我索尼是因为
At your service. They call me Sonny on account
我这个非常阳光的性格
of my sunny disposition.
我觉得这名字很适合他
You know, I think that name kind of works for him.
这家伙一定是西斯科
'Ey, oh, the guy who must be Cisco.
我的座右铭  对我来说  我的座右铭是
My motto, personally, for me, my motto?
做好人
Be kind.
倒带
Rewind.
-做好人  倒带  -他们还在用录像带
- Be kind. Rewind? - They're still on VHS.
什么
What?
你好  是的  雷好
Hello! Yes, bonjour.
我是哈里森·HP·威尔斯  地球二十五
So I am Harrison H.P. Wells, the Earth-25.
我必须说  我现在心里暖呼呼的
So I must say that it warms me
看着我们因为我们的脸和心而聚在一起
to see us all bonded by our faces and our hearts.
你看他那围巾  我喜欢这围巾
You see his scarf? I like that scarf.
我自己也得弄个
Gonna get myself one of them
跟这家伙一样的经典款围巾
classy scarves like this guy.
这可是十美元的围巾呢
That's a $10 scarf right there.
所以  不再多废话了
So anyway, without further ado,
是时候让我用我所写的
it's time for me to commence this meeting
一首诗来开启这次聚会  开始了
with one of my poems, so... allez.
我不曾认识你
I never knew you.
-不曾尝过你  -尝啊
- I never taste you. - Mm, taste.
不曾闻过你
Never smelled you.
直到我做过  现在我上瘾了
Until I do. And now I am hooked-ed.
真骚
Saucy.
那么  你这首诗是讲什么的
And, uh, what is this poem about?
-面包  -真是很深奥啊
- Bread. - Oh, deep connection.
食物可以滋养灵魂
Food can feed the soul.
我之前曾经和一个热腾腾的苹果派有...
You know, I once had this experience with a hot apple pie--
好了  你知道吗  这一侧
Okay, you know what? That's enough sharing
分享的已经足够多了
from this side of the table.
让别人分享一下如何
How about we let somebody else share?
哈里  该你上了
Harry, you have the floor.
-没门  -哈里
- No chance. - Harry.
-不行  -来吧
- No way. - Come on.
-算了吧  -开始讲吧
- Come on. - Do the intro.
为什么  不
Why? No.
-我才不干  -哈里
- I'm not gonna. - Harry.
-什么  -你必须得
- What? - You have to do
懂得分享才能获得帮助  好吗
the sharing if you want the helping, okay?
开始吧  哈里
Allez, Harry.
-我叫哈里  -你好吗  哈里
- I'm Harry. - How you doin', Harry?
-雷好  哈里  -好呀  哈里
- Bonjour, Harry. - Howdy, Harry.
我们知道他的名字
We know his name.
那么...
So, uh...
是这么回事
here's the thing.
我正在失去我的智力
I'm losing my intelligence.
不是吧
No.
而作为威尔斯  你知道我们的智力
And as Wellses, you know how very important
有多么的重要  所以我想请你们帮助
our intelligence is, and so I'm asking for your help
恢复我的智力  这样我就可以踢...
to get my intelligence back so I can kick some--
我就可以帮助小队
So I can help my team.
你们能帮我吗
Will you help me do that?
当然可以了  哈里
Non. Non, mais of course, Harry.
我们当然会帮他了  我们会帮你
Of course we will help him. We will help you.
打开你的心扉  我们就打开你的思想
Open your heart. We'll open your mind.
来吧  咱们开始吧
Come on, let's do this.
-好  -真棒
- Okay. - Lovely.
巴仔  我们到市场了
Hey, Bar, we're at the market.
如果找到她我们就告诉你
We'll let you know if we find her.
-明白了  -阿姆内特曾经在这里工作吗
- Copy that. - Amunet used to work here?
她做什么  装袋吗
What did she do, bag groceries?
最起码不是贩卖人口
At least it's not human trafficking.
咱们四处看看
Let's look around.
听着  当我告诉你
Hey, look, when I told you
要看看别的道路
to look in a different direction
来找你的那个自我
to find your alter ego,
我不是让你跟罪犯合作
I didn't mean team up with a criminal.
我明白你的意思
I know how that probably looks.
是么  我怎么觉得你想让我们
Yeah, it looks like you want us to work
跟阿姆内特·布莱克合作
with Amunet Black so she can help you
这样她就能帮你解决冰霜杀手的麻烦
with your Killer Frost problem.
我是说  这事你怎么不跟大伙提出来呢
I mean, why weren't you up front with the team about that?
因为我觉得  如果我有自己的理由
Because I thought they'd say no
他们会说不
if I had my own reasons.
况且  事实上我真的认为
Besides, I actually really do think
阿姆内特能帮到我们
Amunet can help us
并帮我解决冰霜杀手的麻烦
and help me with my Killer Frost problem.
具体能怎么帮你
Well, how exactly can she help you?
去年  我在对付冰霜杀手时
Last year, when I was having trouble getting a handle
遇到了麻烦  向她求助
on Killer Frost, I went to her.
她在我身上用了某种黑科技
She used a black market piece of tech on me,
一台连接器  帮我和冰霜杀手分开了
a splicer, helped me split Killer Frost.
所以你就期待着她还有这技术
And you're hoping she still has this tech.
之前起效了  还会再次起效的
It worked before. It could work again.
好吧  凯特琳  你得通知队友
Well, Caitlin, you got to tell the team.
我的天
Damn.
有人看过《茉莉的牌局》吗
Somebody saw "Molly's Game"
等一下
Hang on a second.
中城警局  这是违法行为
CCPD. This is an illegal operation.
所有人出去
Everybody out of the room.
莱斯莉
Leslie.
小凯
Caitie.
用你机智的小脑袋
Leave it to your crafty little brain
去查出我暗藏的秘密吧
to figure out my dark secret.
你来干嘛
What are you doing here?
跟你摊牌  我知道你还活着
Calling your bluff. I knew you were still alive.
没人杀得了我
No one could kill me.
这口音怎么回事
What's with the accent?
这是我伪装的一部分  我得融进来
It's part of my disguise. Had to blend in.
现在我不过是个普通的美国金发女孩
Now I'm just your average American blonde
靠正当收入生活
making an honest living.
比之前正当了  对吧
Well, a more honest living, yeah?
况且  俗话说得好
Besides, you know what they say.
江山易改  本性难移
A zebra never changes its stripes.
闪电侠
Flash.
哦  闪电侠
Oh! Flash. You really do stop
你真的阻止了城里所有的罪行  不是吗
all the crime in the city, don't you?
但今天不行
But not today.
我们不是来打架的
We're not here to fight.
我们需要你的帮助
We need your help.
快看呐
Oh, look!
你的衣服有一个隐藏的小洞
A little hidey-hole for your outfit.
打扰一下  你好像
Hi, excuse me. You don't seem
不是很担心迪沃
too concerned that DeVoe is about to launch
要向太空发射一堆卫星
a bunch of satellites into space
以重启我们所有人的大脑
that are gonna reset all of our brains.
不  亲爱的  我觉得非常困扰
Oh, no, my dear. I find it very troubling.
教授要把全世界的人都变成傻瓜
The professor turning everyone in the world into a dimwit
是很悲剧的
is tragic.
这很棒
It's brilliant.
但很悲剧
But tragic.
所以你愿意跟我们合作
So will you work with us?
帮我们制止迪沃
Help us stop DeVoe?
只是
Just...
那个东西
that thing--
你为什么还穿着它
why do you still have it on?
我的
My--
它能保护我的身份
It helps me protect my identity.
不  它做的不怎么样
No.It's doing a terrible job.
-什么  -是的  你看
- What? - Yes, you see,
禁欲的下颌轮廓  贵族的形象
that stoic jawline, patrician profile.
很明显你就是我从监狱长手中
You're so obviously the speedster I tried
想办法买到的极速者
to procure from the warden.
愿他安息
May he RIP.
-来吧  -我这就脱
- Come on. - I'm doing it.
-你好  帅哥  -你好
- Hello, handsome. - Hello.
想想看闪电侠在我手里了
To think I had the Flash in my grasp.
这笔买卖我本可以大赚一笔
What a pretty penny I could have gotten for that sale.
-阿姆内特  -在
- Amunet. - Yes.
别跑题
Focus.
好的  所以说
Okay. So...
一方面  我比团队成员更独裁
On the one hand, I am more dictator than team player.
但另一方面  迪沃教授的愚民
But on the other... Professor DeVoe stupefying
会对生意很不利
the planet would be bad for business.
所以我同意合作
So I'll do it.
不幸的是  有个条件
Unfortunately, there is a but.
我就知道
There usually is one.
你瞧  在生活中  我知道
You see, in life, I have found
并不是越大的就越好
that bigger isn't always better.
但在这种情况下
But in this case...
你需要更多的碎片
You need more shards to take out something
来取出卫星大小的东西
the size of a satellite.
你之前从哪里得到这些的
So where'd you get those?
粒子加速器爆炸那晚
From the plane I was on the night
我工作的飞机上
the particle accelerator exploded.
它们放在通往军事设施
They were in the cargo bay
途中的货舱内
en route to a military facility.
而最终也没能到达目的地
Which conveniently never made it to its final destination.
你知道的  通常我会直接
You see, normally I would just pop down
到我的储物仓库去拿我的大家伙
to my storage locker to grab my big job stash,
但上周  一个淘气的男孩  或者女孩
but last week, a naughty boy--or girl
或者非二元性别的人
or non-binary gendered individual--
溜了进去洗劫了那地方
snuck in and robbed the place.
好吧  我们应该检查一下你的储物仓库
Yeah, well, we should check out your storage unit.
或许会有些线索
There might still be some clues.
我想我在公寓里有一套旧的鉴证员装备
I think I have an old CSI kit back at the apartment.
很好  你们人真好
Great. You guys are so good.
抱歉  打扰一下  你要去哪里
Sorry, excuse me. Where are you going?
去厨房喝点茶
To the kitchen for a spot of tea?
我来带路
Why don't I take you?
你在这里准备食物
Oh. You prepare food in here?
不是很卫生
It's not very sanitary.
我想和你单独谈谈
I wanted to talk to you alone.
我带你来这里不仅仅是要帮我们阻止迪沃
I didn't just bring you here to help us stop DeVoe.
别有用心的动机
An ulterior motive.
多么隐秘而又中肯
How furtive and apropos.
说到底  为什么还要
After all, why go through all the hassle
不顾一切麻烦来找我  冰霜杀手
of procuring me when Killer Frost
可以很容易的用冰霜攻击
could quite easily just ice blast
把那些卫星打下来
those satellites down?
冰霜杀手消失了  自从迪沃
Killer Frost is gone. I haven't been able
对她用了超能力之后
to get her to appear ever since DeVoe
我就没法让她出现了
used one of his powers on her.
记得去年我找你的时候
Remember last year when I came to you
是因为冰霜杀手占据了上风
because Killer Frost was taking over?
你修复了我
You fixed me.
我的转化模块基因连接器
My transmodular genetic splicer.
我需要再用一次连接器
I need to use that splicer again.
凯特
Caitie.
我那么愿意帮助你和你的小伙伴
One of the reasons why I was so willing to help you
对付那个教授的原因之一
and your friends with your professor situation
是因为  直白的说...
is because, well, quite literally...
这些对我也有好处
it also benefits me.
但给你我的连接器  对我没有好处
But giving you my splicer, not as beneficial.
做个交易如何
What if I make you a deal?
你把连接器给我
You give me the splicer.
冰霜杀手和我就帮你一个忙
Killer Frost and I will do you one favor.
这个邀请很吸引人
Oh, that is a tempting offer.
但不幸的是  我的连接器和我
But unfortunately my splicer was stashed right alongside
其他的碎片一起藏起来了
my additional shards.
在你被洗劫的仓库
In your ransacked storage unit.
好  找到你碎片的时候
Okay, wherever we find your shards,
连接器也会出现
we should also find the splicer.
-没错  -那成交吗
- Ding, ding, ding. - So do we have a deal?
我们一旦找到它你就把连接器给我们吗
You'll give me the splicer as soon as we recover it?
我还会在上面打个蝴蝶结
I'll even tie a little bow on it.
女士们先生们  抓好你们的假发和钥匙
Ladies and gentlemen, hang on to your wigs and keys.
开始吧  哈里  转向这个肯定是西斯科的家伙
Here we go. Harry, turn to him, the guy who must be Cisco.
-表达内心  -对  而且最好接着用
- Express yourself. - Yes, it is best you commence
"我感觉"这种陈述方式来表达
with the "I feel" Statements.
比如我感觉到渴望  我感觉到兴奋这种
Wow, like "I feel a yearnin"" Or "I feel aroused""
好了  怎么
Okay, how--
这怎么会让我比迪沃聪明
how is this gonna make me smarter than DeVoe?
又是迪沃
'Ey! Again with DeVoe.
你们为什么那么执着于那混蛋
Why you so hung up on this mamalooch?
我觉得那个迪沃  对于你而言  是一个
I think that DeVoe, for you, this is a guy
有着...  他就像你身上的水蛭
that has--well, he's like a leech upon you
一直在吸血
sucking and sucking
吸血  吸血  吸血
and sucking and sucking and sucking.
你最后剩下的就是疑问
And all you are left with... is doubt.
我喜欢这个表达  自然  凶牙利齿
I like that. Nature, red in tooth and claw.
俗话说要了解一个人的行为
You know, they say to understand a man's actions,
就要了解他的心
you got to understand his heart.
好吧  提问
Oh, okay, question.
你怎么去了解一个
How do you understand the heart
精神错乱疯子的内心
of a deranged maniac?
这个肯定是西斯科的家伙说得好
That guy who must be Cisco makes a good point here.
我们一起闭上眼
Let's all close our eyes and...
花一点时间想像我们都是反社会的人
take a moment and imagine that we are all sociopaths
-致力于征服世界  -是的
- trying to conquer the world. - Ah, yes.
这是...
What is--
哈里  你也加入进来  快点
Oh, mais, Harry. Go on, allez.
把自己当成迪沃
Put yourself in DeVoe's shoes.
闭上眼  哈里
Close your eyes, Harry.
现在你看到了什么
Now what do you see?
闻到了什么
What do you smell?
感受到了什么
How do you feel?
无语  愚蠢
Dumb. Dumb.
这并没有让我聪明
This is not making me any smarter.
但你不聪明吗  哈里
But aren't you smarter, Harry?
你要把你的好斗情绪
You must channel your aggression
与爱相连
into love.
我感觉你在嘲笑我
I feel like you're mocking me.
他用了"我感觉"句式  赢了  赢了
Oh! An "I Feel" Statement! Winner, winner.
不错不错  进步了
All right, all right, all right, progress!
-那就这样...  -等等
- On that note... - Wait, wait.
我们没结束吧
We're not done here, are we?
-结束了  -我们结束了
- Yeah, we're done, - Yeah, we're done.
-是的  已经结束了  -不不不
- Oui, oui, c'est fini. - No, no, no.
-没有什么结束了  -哈里...
- Nothing's fini. - Now, Harry...
俗话说  只工作不玩
You know what they say about all work and no play.
就挤压了制造爱的时间
Leaves no time for making whoopee.
他就这么走了
And there he goes.
HP  拜托  我们还没有结束
Look, H.P., come on, we're not done.
-我们什么都没做呢  -不不  老兄  抱歉
- We haven't done anything. - Non, non, mon frere, desole.
分手是如此甜蜜的悲伤  但我一定与你再会
Parting, such sweet sorrow, but I must bid you adieu.
来自地球2的哈里  拜拜
Harry from Earth-2, adieu.
哈里  你需要的一切...
'Ey, Harry, everything you need...
都在这里了
you got it right in there.
记住  你令人难以置信
Remember, you're unbelievable.
拉蒙  再提醒我...
Ramon, remind me again...
巨大的同义词是什么
what's--what's another word for "Huge"?
庞大
"Colossal""
庞大  很好  谢谢你
Colossal. Great, thank you.
这真是对时间庞大的浪费
This...was a colossal waste of time!
到了
Here we are.
这就是你藏东西的地方吗
This is where you kept your stash?
我发现了什么
Well, I got something.
锁销上有某种物质
Some kind of substance on the lock pin.
看上去他们是用这个破门而入的
Looks like they applied it to break the door open.
年轻人  大卫·卡鲁索都比不上你呢
Young man, David Caruso's got nothing on you.
因《霹雳战警》走红的男演员
客气了
Thanks.
这是什么
What is it?
酸  氰化物
Acid? Cyanide?
是炭疽吗
Oh, oh! Is it anthrax?
血毒液
Hematoxic venom.
那个难看肮脏的流氓竟敢背叛我
Oh, that grotty, manky, plug-ugly prat dare betray me?
看起来她知道是谁干的了
I take it she knows who did this.
没错  你也知道了
Yep, and so do you.
-诺瓦克  -我一定要让
- Norvock. - And I guarantee
那个脑袋里长蛇的尝到苦头
that snake for brains will suffer.
如果诺瓦克觉得可以从我这偷东西
If Norvock thinks he can steal from me
并逃之夭夭  那他肯定计划着其他事
and get away with it, he has got another thing coming.
真不敢相信
I can't believe this is happening.
卫星没有在城市捕获到任何你的
Satellite's not picking up any of your alnico metal
-亚力可金属信号  -诺瓦克可能是个笨蛋
- anywhere in the city. - Norvock may be a moron,
但他不至于笨到
but he's not stupid enough to keep
把东西放在光天化日之下
the stash out in the open.
-有发现了吗  -没有
- Hey, did you find anything? - Nope.
诺瓦克和盒子都不在区域内
Norvock and the boxers weren't at the ring anymore.
当然不在
Of course not!
因为你和你这帮英雄们提醒他
Because you and your gang of heroes tipped him off
有事情发生了
that something was up.
你增强了中城上方的卫星吗
Have you expanded the satellite beyond Central City?
-是的  -面部识别呢
- Yeah. - What about trying facial recognition?
当然试过了
Yes, of course.
你像上次那样对金属特征
And what about a geological scan
进行了地质扫瞄吗
of the metal signature like last time
或者让西斯科再运行一个算法
or having Cisco run another algorithm to check
检查城里的电磁场
the electromagnetic fields in the city?
凯特琳  这些我都做过了
Yes, Caitlin. I've done all that.
我做了所有的测试
I've run all the tests.
你有点暴躁  冰霜
Bit testy with that, Frost. Just...
我们在尝试所有的方法  好吗
We're doing everything we can, all right?
我们会找到诺瓦克和碎片的
We're gonna find Norvock and the shards.
凯特琳
Caitlin.
这是关于她被偷走的碎片
Is this about her stolen shards...
还是她的科技
or her tech?
什么  什么科技
What? What tech?
阿姆内特有她去年用来
Amunet has splicer technology that she used
分离冰霜杀手的连接器科技
to split Killer Frost last year.
我想再用一次让冰霜杀手出现  但是
I was hoping to use it again to get Killer Frost to come out, but
它和她的金属碎片一起被藏在了储藏箱里
it was hidden with her metal shards in the storage container.
你为什么不告诉我们
Why wouldn't you tell us that?
因为我和阿姆内特说好了
Because I made Amunet a deal.
如果她帮助我  冰霜杀手会帮她一个忙
If she helped me, Killer Frost would do another job for her.
连接器科技不是你唯一的希望
Well, that splicer tech isn't your only hope.
它是  乔  我试过了所有
Yes, it is, Joe. I have tried everything
我能想到的让冰霜杀手出现的方法
that I can think of to get Killer Frost to appear,
这是我最后的机会
and that was my last shot.
她现在彻底消失了
So now she's gone for good.
那些怪人和他们的感受
Those weirdos with their feelings.
我不想谈我的感受了
I'm done talking about my feelings.
你怎么了
What's your problem?
没什么  只是看起来你要
No, it just looked like you were gonna--
这是什么  你在干什么
What is this? What are you doing?
我在清理我的工作站
I am cleaning up my work station
因为我以后再也用不到它了
because I'm not gonna need it anymore
鉴于我没法把我的智力找回来
since I'm not getting my intelligence back.
你不能确定
You don't know that.
我不能确定  我不确定吗
I don't know that? Oh, I don't know that?
拉蒙  事已至此
Ramon, what's done is done.
你这段时间一直忙于委员会的事
You spent all this time bringing this council together
你应该把时间用在帮助小队上
when your time should have been used helping the team.
浪费了你的宝贵时间  我为此
I wasted your valuable time, and for that...
我向你道歉
I apologize.
你这是  怎么了
What are you... What?
-我身上洒了汤吗  -不  没有
- Spill some soup on me? - No, no, no.
只是  刚刚非常真实
It's just, that was... that was very real.
像是个非常真诚的道歉
That was, like, a very -- very genuine apology.
我是认真的
Well, I meant it.
我看得出来  不是讽刺
Well, I can tell. There's no snark.
你没扔东西
You're not throwing anything.
是啊  我没有
You're right. I'm not.
委员会可能帮不到你的智力
The council might not have helped your intelligence,
但我想他们
but I think they...
或许让你发掘出了
might have shown you a little...
同情心
empathy?
塞西尔·霍尔顿地检官说
You know, DA Cecile Horton said
做一个聪明的人还有其它方式
there's other ways to be intelligent.
敞开心扉
Open your heart...
开启心智
Open your mind.
但是我已经太久没有去
But it's been so long since I've been concerned
关注过其他人的感受了
for other people's feelings, though, you know?
你知道吗
You know what?
也许是时候去关心一下别人的感受了
Maybe it is time I consider someone else's feelings.
我感觉
Well, I feel--
-迪沃  -迪沃
- DeVoe. - DeVoe.
对吗  也许委员会说得有道理
Right? Maybe the council had a point.
让我理解迪沃的最好方式
The best way for me to understand DeVoe...
就是站在他的角度思考
put myself in his shoes.
-是的  -这是刚刚你想说的吗
- Yeah. - Is that what you were gonna say?
不  我想说迪沃
No, I was gonna say DeVoe.
-好吧  -很有道理
- Okay. - That makes sense.
-的确  -是的
- It does. - Yeah.
有诺瓦克的消息吗
Hey, anything on Norvock?
没有  但是我有迪沃的新情况
No, but I do have an update on DeVoe.
这是我写好的文章
It's my finished article.
巴里  我和你一样担忧迪沃
Barry, look, I'm just as anxious as you are about DeVoe,
但是我认为我们应该
but I really think that we need to
把消息告诉市民  而不是让他们蒙在鼓里
arm the citizens with information, not shield them from it.
爱瑞丝  我只是
Iris, I'm just...
我这是为了中城和团队好
I'm trying to do what's best for the city and the team.
听着
And look...
我认为实话实说就是最好的方法
I think that telling the truth is what's best.
如果我们告诉他们所有需要考虑的真相
I mean, if we give them all of the facts to consider,
他们会做出正确的选择
they will do the right thing.
但是你怎样能确定呢
But how can you be sure about that?
听着  巴里
Look, Barry...
我不否认你这一年和迪沃的斗争很难  但是
I can't deny that you've had a tough year with DeVoe, but...
他的目标就是把信息从人们手中夺走
his entire goal is to take information away from people.
如果我们不发表这篇文章
If we don't publish this article,
我们就和他一样了
we are no better than he is.
只是  这个...
I just--this is...
我认为这太冒险了
I think it's too risky.
我知道你是这样想的
I know that's how you feel...
我真的希望我们能站在同一战线上
and I really want us to be on the same page.
所以  由你来决定
So... it's your decision.
-爱瑞丝  -我只是希望你记得
- Iris-- - I just want you to remember
闪电侠是希望的灯塔
that The Flash is a beacon of hope
人们总是对他抱有信心
that the people have always put their faith in.
现在到了闪电侠
And now it's time for The Flash
去相信人民的时候了
to put his faith in the people.
你在这里啊
Ah, there you are.
我注意到了你的愤怒和敌意
I couldn't help but notice your anger and hostility.
虽然你是蓝色的  不是红色
Thought your color was blue, not red.
是  我很愤怒  我这几个星期一直很愤怒
Yes, I'm angry. I've been angry for weeks
然而冰霜杀手依旧没有出现
and still no Killer Frost.
而现在诺瓦克把一切都毁了
And now Norvock's ruined everything.
小凯
Oh, Caitie.
我不喜欢看到你如此颓废的样子
I hate to see you so torn up like this.
所以我要告诉你一件
So I'm going to tell you something
能让你高兴的事
that will cheer you up.
那个连接器
That splicer...
没有治好你
did not cure you.
-什么  -你...
- What? - Well, you--
你来找我时心灰意冷
you had come to me so broken...
非常迫切
so needy.
于是我就把那玩意儿放到你脑袋上
And so I put that piece of tech on your head, and,
然后啥都没发生
poof, nothing!
它对你并没有起作用
It did not work on you.
你就决定要骗我  而不是实言相告吗
So you decided to lie to me rather than tell me that?
但虽然连接器
But just because the splicer
在技术层面上并没有发挥作用
didn't technically work doesn't mean
并不意味着没产生好的结果
that the results were not the same.
这怎么说  你的话完全说不通
How? That doesn't make any sense.
你是医生  你说呢
You're the doctor. You tell me.
是安慰剂效应
It's a placebo.
看到没
You see?
你的能力一直都在你的体内
It's been inside you the entire time.
小凯  你的能力
Caitie, your power is unlike
与我之前所见过的都不相同
anything I have ever seen before,
没有任何科学仪器或是安慰剂效应
and no science kit or placebo
能解释你为什么...
is going to explain why you--
安慰剂效应
A placebo...
假的
A fake.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
我知道诺瓦克在哪里了
I know exactly where Norvock is.
接到电话我们很意外
We were surprised to get the call.
不应该  现在是我管事了
Shouldn't be. I'm running things now.
阿姆内特是过去时了
Amunet's gone.
但她留下了一件非常有价值的东西
But she did leave behind something very valuable.
比钢坚硬三十倍
30 times stronger than steel.
可以随心所欲组装成想要的样子
You can assemble them in any shape you like.
最厉害的是
And best of all...
其中注入了足够的潜在能量
they're loaded with enough potential energy
能夷平一座城市
to flatten a city.
-我们知道诺瓦克在哪儿了  -就在我以为
- We know where Norvock is. - Just when I thought
我已经考虑到所有
I'd considered every option
诺瓦克可能藏身的地点后
for where Norvock might be skulking,
我记起来每当条子
I remembered whenever the fuzz
盯上我们的哪笔交易时
used to be onto one of our deals,
我就会散布谣言  爆出一个假的
I would plant a rumor that it was going down
交易地点
at a false location.
虚晃一枪  好躲过"条子"的追查
Ah, a fake-out to keep "The fuzz" Off your tracks.
所以我认为诺瓦克就在那里
So that's where we think Norvock is,
在被废弃的雷诺兹堡分局
in the abandoned Reynolds substation.
在地下  所以碎片才没有
Underground. That's why the shards weren't
在卫星上登记
registering on the satellite.
好  不如我们三个先去拿你们的碎片
All right, why don't the three of us go get your shards?
然后我们武装起来  去解决掉迪沃的卫星
Then we'll be armed and ready to take out DeVoe's satellites.
-我也要去  -我去拿冷冻枪
- I'm coming too. - I'll get the cold gun.
很好  一次小组突袭
Oh, goody, a group foray.
给诺瓦克收尸的事留给我
Dibs on cashing in Norvock's chips.
不行不行不行
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
-不许杀人  -我同意加入这个团队时
- No killing. - That was not a stipulation
可没答应过这一条
when I agreed to join this crew.
阿姆内特听着  我知道你以前的做事方法
Okay, Amunet, look, I know how you usually work,
但我能迅速地处理好此事  而且没有伤亡
but I can handle this fast and without an casualties.
好吧  清理金属上的血渍
Okay. 'Tis a bit time-consuming
确实比较费工夫
to remove blood from metal.
交易终止了  那些碎片属于阿姆内特
This deal's off. Those shards belong to Amunet.
要是那个老巫婆
Well, if that decrepit hag
不想碎片被偷  那她就不应该告诉我
didn't want them stolen, she shouldn't have told me
-她把碎片藏在哪里  -你说我老
- where she hid them. - Decrepit?
人不大口气可不小
That's a big word for such a small man.
阿姆内特  这里交给我就行
Amunet, I've got this.
对女人来说  有些事
There are some things that a woman
决不能假手他人
just cannot delegate.
我们说好的  不能杀人
We agreed, no killing.
那这就让接下来轻松多了
That'll make this next part easy.
乔  碎片在车里  我们不能让他们跑了
Joe, the shards are in there. We can't let them get away.
巴里  出什么事了
Barry, what's going on?
你的生命体征要突破天际了
Your vitals are going through the roof.
-毒液  -和阿姆内特
- Venom! - Like the venom
保险柜上的毒液一样  交给我吧
on Amunet's locker. I'm on it.
你和你脑袋里的东西一样恶劣
You are just as vile as that thing in your head.
做这玩意儿可费了不少工夫
Took a while to get this made.
现在你再也不能用那些东西对付我了
Now you can't use those things against me anymore.
你一直都看不起我
You always underestimated me.
凯特琳  退后  这里
Caitlin, get back! Over here!
-爱瑞丝  -巴里  这么强力的
- Iris... - Barry, there is no antidote
超能力者毒液没有解药
for meta-human venom that potent.
你得在毒液到达心脏之前
You're gonna have to phase through it now
把它们振动出来
before it gets to your heart.
我要没子弹了
I'm running out of ammo.
他们会在我打中他们之前打中我的
They'll hit me before I hit them with this.
该死
Damn.
我们一直处在错误的角度看待问题
We've been looking at this from the wrong direction.
你要干什么
What--what are you doing?
漂亮
Nice!
我一直都不理解你的超能力
I've never understood your superpower.
你是人长出了条蛇呢  还是蛇长出了个人
Are you a man with a snake or a snake with a man?
阿姆内特  别杀他
Amunet! Don't kill him.
死都是便宜他了
He's more than earned it.
这不是为了他  是为了你
It's not about him. It's about you.
凯特琳
Caitlin.
阿姆内特  你有良善的一面
Amunet, there is a good part of you.
我对此深信不疑
I truly believe that.
好吧
Fine.
但这条蛇必须除掉
But the snake has got to go.
跟诺瓦克一样  我也得走了
Like Norvock, I must be on my way.
阿姆内特  别
Amunet, no! Hey!
你一走  我们就没法阻止迪沃的卫星了
You leave, there's no way we can stop DeVoe's satellites.
她从来都不想帮我们
She was never gonna help us.
她只想要回她的金属
She just wanted her metal.
说实话  我确实考虑过
Oh...truthfully, I did consider it.
真的  但老玩家知道什么时候该收手
I did. But a good player knows when to fold.
那位教授绝对比我技高一筹  所以
And the professor certainly has a better hand, so...
别想拦住我
don't try to stop me.
毕竟  我弹药满满的
After all, I am packing.
你走到任何地方  迪沃的卫星都会找到你
There is no where you can go that DeVoe's satellites
如果你现在离开了
won't reach you. If you leave now,
你的大脑会和我们一样熔掉
you'll be mind melted just like the rest of us.
有道理
Good point.
声明一下  不是我在帮忙
Just for the record, this is not me helping.
完全是自我保护
It is entirely self-preservation.
由弹片和我的超能力
Filled with shrapnel and bound with
神秘原理组成的
my meta-human je ne sais quoi.
拔出碎片  扔掉
Pull a shard, throw it, it will deliver
会产生巨大破坏的爆炸
one savage concussive blow.
但机会只有一次
But you only get one shot.
我知道你不会浪费的
I know you won't waste it.
去拯救世界吧  亲爱的
Go save the world, my darling.
她走了
And she's gone.
至少她没让我们空手而归
At least she didn't leave us empty-handed.
蛇眼
Eye snakes.
为什么非要是蛇眼
Why did it have to be eye snakes?
相信我  听起来一点都不酷
Trust me, man, it wasn't as cool as it sounds.
各位  抱歉我得和阿姆内特合作
Guy's, I'm sorry I got so worked up with Amunet around.
-没关系  -阿姆内特确实给了我们
- It's okay. - Yeah, and Amunet did give us
磁钢合金抛射弹
the alnico metal projectile bomb.
我依然认为是阻止迪沃的最好机会
I still think it's our best bet at stopping DeVoe.
-我们只需要想明白怎么使用  -是啊
- We just need to figure out how to fire it. - Yeah.
西斯科  你能打开缺口传送那东西吗
Cisco, can you breach that thing?
我  不行
Me? No way.
我的能量场达不到外太空
My energy field can't even reach outer space.
好吧  我们的想另一个办法了
'Kay, well, we need to find
我们得在迪沃
another solution, and we need to find it
发射卫星之前找到办法
before DeVoe launches those satellites.
实际上  多亏了拉蒙
Well, actually, thanks to Ramon
和哈里森委员会  关于迪沃为什么还没
and the Council of Harrisons, we may have an idea
发射卫星  我们有一个想法
about why DeVoe has not yet launched his satellites.
他站在迪沃的角度思考
He put himself in DeVoe's shoes.
我想  如果我是坐在漂浮椅子上的
And I thought, well, if I was this ultra-genius
超级天才  我会是什么感觉
moving around in a floating chair, how would I feel?
你没有感觉  你会反社会
You'd feel nothing. You'd be sociopathic.
对  但是
Right, but...
我不会认为自己反社会
to me, I wouldn't consider myself sociopathic, right?
我所有的行为
No, all my actions would be driven
会被我最在意的事情驱动
by the one thing that I care most about, right?
所以如果没有行动
And-- - So if you're not acting--
如果没有行动  那么我就
If I'm not acting, then I don't have
没有我最在意的事情
the one thing that I care most about...
我的妻子
my wife.
你们需要我再解释一下吗
You guys need me to walk you through this? So this--
不了  我们明白  哈里
No, we--we get it, Harry.
有点复杂  不过明白了
It's kind of complicated, but okay,
我就信你了
I'll take you at your word.
实际上  这让我想得很累
Actually, that took a lot out of me.
我去睡一觉
I'm gonna go have a nap.
我们可以继续这个思路
Well, we can work with that idea.
我会打开卫星
Yeah, I will fire up the satellite
看是否能找到马尔利泽
and see if I can find Marlize.
我去想办法怎么发射
And I'll start figuring out how to launch
这神奇的暗物质聚合金属榴霰弹
this psychic dark matter-infused metal shrapnel bomb.
小菜一碟
No big deal.
乔  在去中城警局之前
Joe, do you want to get a cup of coffee with me
想和我去喝一杯咖啡吗
before you go back to CCPD?
今天过后我确实需要些咖啡因
I could use some caffeine after today.
我知道你不会听腻
I know you don't get tired
但是我还要说
of hearing it, but...
-你是对的  -看错了阿姆内特
- you were right. - Well, not about Amunet.
她还是背叛了我们
She still betrayed us.
但她知道迪沃的本质
But she knew the truth about DeVoe, and...
她最终做出了不那么自私的决定
she ultimately made a selfless decision
给了我们投射弹来帮助我们
to help us by giving us the projectile.
我对中城有信心  爱瑞丝
And I do have faith in Central City, Iris.
因为我知道  这城市每一个市民的
Because I know that at the core of every citizen
内心深处是  有良知的
of this city is... something good.
我知道他们读了你的文章后
And I know they'll feel the same way
也会这么想
when they read your article.
我们告诉其他成员吧
Let's tell the team.
你确定你想这么做
Are you sure you want to do this?
你想让我发表那篇文章
You want me to publish my article?
毫无疑问
Without a doubt.
我们在一起总是更强大  最好一起
We're always stronger, better together.
吻我
Kiss me.
谢谢
Thank you.
我请你  我坚持
Ah-ah, this one's on me. I insist.
好  我为什么有如此待遇
Nice. What'd I do to deserve that?
因为你给了我需要的建议
That's for giving me the advice I needed
即使我不愿意听
even when I didn't want to hear it.
当你有了孩子  你会习惯给建议的
Well, when you raise kids, you get used to giving advice.
当初我相信
So I was convinced
连接器技术是找回
that that splicer technology was the key
冰霜杀手的关键
to getting Killer Frost back.
但是我错了
But I was wrong.
连接器只是个安慰剂
The splicer was just a placebo,
哄骗我显现出
and it tricked me into manifesting
我想的外表上的结果
those somatic results that I wanted.
你从阿姆内特那里学到的
You learned that from Amunet?
我以为答案在科学里
I thought the answer was in science,
但是永远不会找到
but it was never gonna be there.
-现在怎么办呢  -我会采纳你的建议
- So what now? - I'm gonna take your advice.
我会从完全相反的方向看问题
I'm gonna look in a completely different direction.
找到冰霜杀手的关键不在外面
The key to finding Killer Frost is not out there.
在这里
It's in here.
-爱瑞丝  怎么了  -巴里
- Iris, what's happening? - Barry?
-什么  -是中城
- What? - It's the city.
-什么  -我发表了文章
- What? - I posted my article,
他们在回复
and they're responding.
什么意思  他们相信你
What do you mean? They believed you?
不止如此  他们想帮忙  看
More than that. They want to help. Look.
这人说他两天前在第五大道和克诺路看到迪沃
This guy says he saw DeVoe on 5th and Knoll two days ago.
另一个人说在克莱森特和第十大道
Yeah, and another guy on Crescent and 10th.
太棒了
This is great.
爱瑞丝  这意味着迪沃无法再躲着我们了
Iris, this means DeVoe can't hide from us anymore.